question_data = [
    {"question":"In Norse mythology, Thor once dressed as a woman.","correct_answer":"True"},
    {"question":"Rannamaari was a sea demon that haunted the people of the Maldives and had to be appeased monthly with the sacrifice of a virgin girl.","correct_answer":"True"},
    {"question":"According to Greek Mythology, Atlas was an Olympian God.","correct_answer":"False"},
    {"question":"Janus was the Roman god of doorways and passageways.","correct_answer":"True"},
    {"question":"In Greek mythology, Hera is the goddess of harvest.","correct_answer":"False"},
    {"question":"The Japanese god Izanagi successfully returned his wife Izanami from the Underworld.","correct_answer":"False"},
    {"question":"According to Norse mythology, Loki is a mother.","correct_answer":"True"},
    {"question":"A wyvern is the same as a dragon.","correct_answer":"False"},
    {"question":"The Roman god Jupiter was first known as Zeus to the Greeks.","correct_answer":"True"},
    {"question":"According to Greek Mythology, Zeus can control lightning","correct_answer":"True"}
]